mailmarketer.in 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Guarantee

At Mail Marketer, we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use our website. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to the Mail Marketer website, products and services that are located in, but not limited to the mailmarkter.in domains.

### Information Collection and Use

Mail Marketer is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Mail Marketer collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Our website offers several opportunities for visitors to register for promotional and informational mailings, online webinars and resources, and for assistance in evaluating our software and services. These registration forms enable users to opt-in to Mail Marketer's mailing lists and require users to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this contact information to send information about our company and our products and services. Notice is given at the point of collection to enable users to choose whether or not they consent to the usage terms. Those who have signed up and subsequently wish to withdraw their participation may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time (see the choice/opt-out section below).

We also keep track of activity on our website via log files stored on our web servers. We collect information such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. We use our logs of your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our website and to tailor our product and service offerings to you.

### Security and Privacy

We take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your data by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. When we collect sensitive account information such as credit card numbers, we protect its transmission through the use of encryption such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Mail Marketer takes care to reinforce the importance of our website visitors' security and privacy among our employees. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only.

We will never share, sell, or rent your data with third parties for their promotional use. If required by your company, we sign NDA agreement.

### Links

Some of our sites provide links to third-party websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertising partners. While on these sites, Mail Marketer or its partners may collect information about you. Because Mail Marketer does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information.
